[
  {
    "question": "ばく",
    "choices": ["中国", "韓国", "インド", "ベトナム"],
    "answer": "中国"
  },
  {
    "question": "瀬戸大将",
    "choices": ["愛知", "高知", "山梨", "熊本"],
    "answer": "愛知"
  },
  {
    "question": "さがり",
    "choices": ["岡山", "香川", "沖縄", "長崎"],
    "answer": "岡山"
  },
  {
    "question": "すねこすり",
    "choices": ["岡山", "徳島", "福島", "宮城"],
    "answer": "岡山"
  },
  {
    "question": "キジムナー",
    "choices": ["沖縄", "大分", "奈良", "三重"],
    "answer": "沖縄"
  },
  {
    "question": "二口女",
    "choices": ["下総", "上総", "常総", "南総"],
    "answer": "下総"
  },
  {
    "question": "濡れ女",
    "choices": ["新潟", "奈良", "宮城", "高知"],
    "answer": "新潟"
  },
  {
    "question": "濡れ女",
    "choices": ["福島", "埼玉", "鹿児島", "岩手"],
    "answer": "福島"
  },
  {
    "question": "つるべおとし",
    "choices": ["京都", "富山", "沖縄", "徳島"],
    "answer": "京都"
  },
  {
    "question": "家鳴り",
    "choices": ["京都", "埼玉", "鹿児島", "岩手"],
    "answer": "京都"
  },
  {
    "question": "竹切狸",
    "choices": ["京都", "滋賀", "福井", "佐賀"],
    "answer": "京都"
  },
  {
    "question": "竹切狸",
    "choices": ["静岡", "鹿児島", "埼玉", "長野"],
    "answer": "静岡"
  },
  {
    "question": "竹切狸",
    "choices": ["鳥取", "山口", "秋田", "愛媛"],
    "answer": "鳥取"
  },
  {
    "question": "天井なめ",
    "choices": ["群馬", "鹿児島", "埼玉", "長野"],
    "answer": "群馬"
  },
  {
    "question": "山爺",
    "choices": ["高知", "石川", "沖縄", "岡山"],
    "answer": "高知"
  },
  {
    "question": "袖引小僧",
    "choices": ["埼玉", "群馬", "北海道", "熊本"],
    "answer": "埼玉"
  },
  {
    "question": "カシャボ",
    "choices": ["和歌山", "山口", "秋田", "愛媛"],
    "answer": "和歌山"
  },
  {
    "question": "",
    "choices": ["三重", "鹿児島", "静岡", "熊本"],
    "answer": "三重"
  },
  {
    "question": "蟹坊主",
    "choices": ["山梨", "鹿児島", "静岡", "熊本"],
    "answer": "山梨"
  },
  {
    "question": "一反木綿",
    "choices": ["鹿児島", "三重", "栃木", "山形"],
    "answer": "鹿児島"
  },
  {
    "question": "ガラッパ",
    "choices": ["鹿児島", "山梨", "高知", "石川"],
    "answer": "鹿児島"
  },
  {
    "question": "豆腐小僧",
    "choices": ["鹿児島", "群馬", "埼玉", "石川"],
    "answer": "鹿児島"
  },
  {
    "question": "呼子",
    "choices": ["島根", "高知", "佐賀", "茨城"],
    "answer": "島根"
  },
  {
    "question": "猫又",
    "choices": ["新潟", "青森", "埼玉", "京都"],
    "answer": "新潟"
  },
  {
    "question": "雷獣",
    "choices": ["新潟", "長崎", "和歌山", "千葉"],
    "answer": "新潟"
  },
  {
    "question": "雷獣",
    "choices": ["長野", "長崎", "和歌山", "千葉"],
    "answer": "長野"
  },
  {
    "question": "枕返し",
    "choices": ["静岡", "福井", "沖縄", "長野"],
    "answer": "静岡"
  },
  {
    "question": "傘化け",
    "choices": ["鳥取", "三重", "奈良", "佐賀"],
    "answer": "鳥取"
  },
  {
    "question": "かみきり",
    "choices": ["東京", "和歌山", "兵庫", "北海道"],
    "answer": "東京"
  },
  {
    "question": "小豆はかり",
    "choices": ["東京", "奈良", "福島", "沖縄"],
    "answer": "東京"
  },
  {
    "question": "朱の盤",
    "choices": ["福島", "和歌山", "山形", "香川"],
    "answer": "福島"
  },
  {
    "question": "ろくろくび",
    "choices": ["福島", "高知", "鹿児島", "岐阜"],
    "answer": "福島"
  },
  {
    "question": "砂かけ婆",
    "choices": ["奈良", "沖縄", "山形", "佐賀"],
    "answer": "奈良"
  },
  {
    "question": "砂かけ婆",
    "choices": ["兵庫", "高知", "鹿児島", "岐阜"],
    "answer": "兵庫"
  },
  {
    "question": "コロポックル",
    "choices": ["北海道", "東京", "長野", "熊本"],
    "answer": "北海道"
  }
]
